Hydro Volter

My Resume

Tech Enthusiast, Community Manager, Music Lover, Conversable Figure

United Kingdom

hydrovolter.ml/

B

@hydrovolter

github.com/Hydrovolter

EDUCATION

Study ProgramInstitution/Place of Education

WORK EXPERIENCE

Emerald Practice

462+ Members

06/2022 - Present

Diamond Drafts EU 424+ Members

06/2022 - Present

Cherry's Room

132+ Members

04/2022 - Present

The Wumpus Galaxy

95+ Members

07/2019 - Present

Quantum Society

852+ Members

03/2020 - 06/2021

MC Creators

132+ Members

04/2022 - 05/2022 Deleted

Cytro's City

124+ Members

09/2019 - 07/2020 Deleted

Gotham's City

111+ Members

07/2019 - 06/2020 Deleted

MORE SMALLER SERVERS

Less than 60 members

Multiple Servers less or around 60 members in size.

SKILLS

Can easily use moderation commands

Can adapt easily and learn quickly

Approachable and easy to converse with

Can conceptualize and think of new ideas/suggestions

Professional and can speak fluent English with correct grammar

Has 2FA Enabled on Discord

Mature and can handle multiple situations

Active on Discord and in servers/chats

On Discord 1-3 hours daily

PERSONAL PROJECTS

My Portfolio (06/2022 - Present)

https://hydrovolter.ml/

Check it out for more information!

Steroffee (04/2022 - 05/2022)

Effective Sales Advertisement

Travel Agency - Castle Dracula (06/2022 - 06/2022)

Another Effective Sales Advertisement

INTRO

Hey, I'm Hydro, and your probably here to view my staff application/resume!

Organization Name

SUMMARY

Dedicated Community Manager with roughly a years worth (taking into consideration of my old account) of management experience. Helps out and streamlines operations for efficiency. Hardworking and resourceful with friendly and professional demeanor. Easy to converse with and to reach out to, and loves to talk.

INTERESTS

Music | Tech

Speaking/Conversing

Conceptualizing

AND MORE! Check out my Website/DM Me!

Interest